Contact

40,vinobha nagar, jaipur 9785608239 (Home) shivanirathore90@yahoo.in

www.linkedin.com/in/shivanirathore-b888597b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Management
Customer Service
Microsoft Office

Certifications

company sectary sip traning

Accounting Foundations: Bookkeeping

Agile Foundations

Business Analysis Foundations Six Sigma Foundations

Shivani Rathore

looking for a change actively Jaipur

Summary

Project management experience project leader give training to team and stake holders.

Experience in different finance domains which is customer service, procurement, Human resources management, account payable, collection.

skilled in oracle, scrum, agile concept, Microsoft Excel and PowerPoint presentation
Achieved many rewards and recognition

Experience

Kotak Mahindra Bank
Executive Assistant
June 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months)
Jaipur Area, India

LUXTURE SURFACE COATINGS PRIVATE LIMITED

Human resource executive July 2017 - May 2018 (11 months) Ajmer Area, India

Toshniwal Industries Pvt. Ltd.
Purchase Executive
May 2016 - June 2017 (1 year 2 months)
Ajmer, Rajasthan, India

Genpact

Process associate
January 2014 - December 2014 (1 year)
Jaipur

my responsibility include build good relation with clients.maintain daily reports of team mates .purchases goods and services as per requirement. bank reconciliation process as well as procurement

I-TECH

customer care executive January 2013 - July 2013 (7 months) Jaipur

to handle the clients issues on engineering subjects

Education

Central University of Rajasthan, Jaipur Master's degree, Business/Commerce, General

TILAK PUBLIC SENIOR SECONDARY SCHOOL

12 th, Business/Commerce, General · (2010 - 2011)

Tilak public school

Senior secondary school, Commerce · (2010 - 2010)